<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Explore Golden Ring</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="address">address</string>
    <string name="place">place</string>
    <string name="descr">description</string>
    <string name="category">category</string>
    <string name="goTo">google.navigation:q=</string>


    <string name="category_yaroslavl">Yaroslavl</string>
    <string name="category_suzdal">Suzdal</string>
    <string name="category_kostroma">Kostroma</string>
    <string name="category_vladimir">Vladimir</string>

    <!--Yaroslavl item name -->

    <string name="yar_MonasterySav_name">Monastery of the Transfiguration of the Saviour</string>
    <string name="yar_JohnBaptist_name">John the Baptist Church at Tolchkovo</string>
    <string name="yar_CathTrans_name">Cathedral of the Transfiguration</string>
    <string name="yar_ArtGov_name">Yaroslavl Art Museum (Governor\'s House)</string>
    <string name="yar_ChurchElijah_name">Church of Elijah the Prophet</string>
    <string name="yar_ArtMetro_name">Yaroslavl Art Museum (Metropolitan Palace)</string>
    <string name="yar_BellTower_name">Bell Tower</string>
    <string name="yar_AnnCath_name">Annunciation Cathedral</string>


    <!-- Yaroslavl item address -->

    <string name="yar_MonasterySav_adr">Yaroslavl, Bogoyavlenskaya pl. 25</string>
    <string name="yar_JohnBaptist_adr">Yaroslavl, 2-ya Zakotoroslnaya nab 69</string>
    <string name="yar_CathTrans_adr">Yaroslavl, Bogoyavleniya pl. 25 building 2</string>
    <string name="yar_ArtGov_adr">Yaroslavl, Volzhskaya nab 23</string>
    <string name="yar_ChurchElijah_adr">Yaroslavl, Sovetskaya pl 7</string>
    <string name="yar_ArtMetro_adr">Yaroslavl, Volzhskaya nab 1</string>
    <string name="yar_BellTower_adr">Yaroslavl, Bogoyavleniya pl. 25 building 2</string>
    <string name="yar_AnnCath_adr">Yaroslavl, Kotoroslnaya nab 2/1</string>


    <!-- Yaroslavl item description -->

    <string name="yar_MonasterySav_des">Founded in the 12th century, the Unesco-listed Monastery of the
        Transfiguration of the Saviour was one of Russia’s richest and best-fortified monasteries by the 16th century.
        The oldest surviving structures, dating from 1516, are the Holy Gate near the main entrance by the river and the Cathedral of the Transfiguration.
        A bird\'s-eye view of Yaroslavl and its rivers can be had by climbing up to the top of the cathedral's bell tower.
        Other buildings house exhibitions on history, ethnography, icons and the Treasures of Yaroslavl Exhibition,
        featuring works of gold, silver and precious gems dating back to the 17th century.</string>
    <string name="yar_JohnBaptist_des">It’s a shame that dingy industrial surroundings discourage most people from visiting Yaroslavl’s
        largest and most unique church – you may recognise it from the 1000-rouble currency note. Protected by Unesco,
        the red-brick structure (built 1671–87) boasts a staggering 15 green-coloured cupolas and some of the most extensive series of frescoes in the Orthodox world.
        It\'s located on the southern bank of the Kotorosl, by the second bridge.
        The church is a 3km (10-minute) car or taxi ride from the centre. By public transport from Bogoyavlenskaya pl,
        take a southbound marshrutka (fixed-route minibus) 87 or bus 19k for four stops, disembarking at the ul Karabulina stop.
        Walk back towards the bridge and turn left at the corner; walk north towards the river and then west to the church (about 500m).
        Note that the church is closed on rainy days to protect the frescoes from moisture.</string>
    <string name="yar_CathTrans_des">This 16th-century cathedral (built 1516) is the oldest free-standing building in Yaroslavl;
        inside are beautiful frescoes from the time of its construction. Designed by an Italian architect, the church combines traditional Russian with Italianate styles,
        such as its arched loggia. You can get a good view of Yaroslavl from its bell tower.
        Note that the cathedral is closed to the public on rainy days to protect its delicate frescoes from moisture.</string>
    <string name="yar_ArtGov_des">The main branch of the city\'s art museum, housed in the restored former governors\' mansion (built 1823),
        showcases two permanent exhibits on 18th- to 20th-century Russian art (individual or joint ticket available), with a large hall dedicated to Impressionist Konstantin Korovin;
        audio guides are available in English. Temporary exhibits – recent ones included art of the post-revolutionary 20th century – have their own admission prices.</string>
    <string name="yar_ChurchElijah_des">The exquisite church that dominates Sovetskaya pl was built by some prominent local fur dealers in 1650. It has some of the Golden Ring’s brightest frescoes,
        done by the ubiquitous painter Gury Nikitin of Kostroma and his school, and detailed exterior tiles. The church is closed on rainy days to protect the frescoes from moisture.</string>
    <string name="yar_ArtMetro_des">The 17th-century former chambers of the metropolitan showcase icons and other religious art from the 13th to 18th centuries.
        Temporary exhibits have separate admission prices; a recent one featured women\'s fashion from 1890 to 1910.</string>
    <string name="yar_BellTower_des">Climb to the top of the bell tower of the Cathedral of the Transfiguration for excellent views over Yaroslavl and the confluence of its two rivers.</string>
    <string name="yar_AnnCath_des">The city\'s main cathedral originally dated from 1215, but was blown up by the Bolsheviks in 1937.
        What you see now is a modern replica erected for Yaroslav’s millennium celebrations in 2010. In front of it, a stone-slab monument marks the spot where Prince Yaroslav founded the city in 1010.
        Past the cathedral, the new Strelka Park stretches right onto the tip of land between the Volga and the Kotorosl Rivers, where the Yaroslavl Millennium Monument was opened in 2010.</string>

    <!-- Suzdal item name -->

    <string name="suz_SaviourMon_name">Saviour Monastery of St Euthymius</string>
    <string name="suz_Kremlin_name">Kremlin</string>
    <string name="suz_WoodArch_name">Museum of Wooden Architecture and Peasant Life</string>
    <string name="suz_NatVirg_name">Nativity of the Virgin Cathedral</string>
    <string name="suz_TorgPl_name">Torgovaya Ploshchad</string>
    <string name="suz_HolyIntConv_name">Holy Intercession Convent</string>
    <string name="suz_ChurchAssump_name">Church of the Assumption of the Mother of God</string>

    <!-- Suzdal item address -->

    <string name="suz_SaviourMon_adr">Suzdal, Lenina ul 135/8</string>
    <string name="suz_Kremlin_adr">Suzdal, Kremlevskaya ul 27</string>
    <string name="suz_WoodArch_adr">Suzdal, Pushkarskaya ul 27B</string>
    <string name="suz_NatVirg_adr">Suzdal, Suzdal kremlin, ul Kremlyovskaya</string>
    <string name="suz_TorgPl_adr">Suzdal, Torgovaya Ploshchad</string>
    <string name="suz_HolyIntConv_adr">Suzdal, Pokrovskaya ul</string>
    <string name="suz_ChurchAssump_adr">Suzdal, ul Kremlyovskaya 8</string>

    <!-- Suzdal item description -->

    <string name="suz_SaviourMon_des">Founded in the 14th century to protect the town’s northern entrance,
        Suzdal\’s biggest monastery grew mighty in the 16th and 17th centuries after Vasily III,
        Ivan the Terrible and the noble Pozharsky family funded impressive new stone buildings and made large land and property acquisitions.
        It was girded with its great brick walls and towers in the 17th century.</string>
    <string name="suz_Kremlin_des">The grandfather of the Moscow Kremlin, this citadel was the 12th-century base of Prince Yury Dolgoruky,
        who ruled the vast northeastern part of Kyivan Rus (and, among other things, founded a small outpost that would eventually become the Russian capital).
        The 1.4km-long earthen ramparts of Suzdal\’s kremlin enclose a few streets of houses and a handful of churches, as well as the main cathedral group on ul Kremlyovskaya.</string>
    <string name="suz_WoodArch_des">This open-air museum across the river from Suzdal\'s kremlin offers a fascinating glimpse into the traditional lives of rural folk in this area.
        Besides log houses, windmills, a barn, and lots of tools and handicrafts, its highlights are the 1756 Transfiguration Church (Преображенская церковь)
        and the simpler 1776 Resurrection Church (Воскресенская церковь). There\'s a similar museum in Kostroma, too.</string>
    <string name="suz_NatVirg_des">The Nativity of the Virgin Cathedral, whose blue domes spangled with gold dominate the front courtyard of the Suzdal kremlin,
        was founded in the 1220s. Only its richly carved lower section is original white stone, however; the rest is 16th-century brick.
        The inside is sumptuous, with 13th- and 17th-century frescoes and 13th-century damascene (gold on copper) west and south doors.</string>
    <string name="suz_TorgPl_des">Suzdal’s Torgovaya pl (Market Sq) is dominated by the pillared Trading Arcades (Торговые ряды; 1806–11) along its western side.
        There are several churches in the immediate vicinity, including the 1739 Kazan Church (Казанская церковь) and the 1720 Resurrection Church (Воскресенская церковь)
        right on the square; the latter's hours are irregular but if it\'s open you can take the precarious climb to the top of the bell tower to be rewarded with wonderful
        views of Suzdal\’s gold-domed skyline.</string>
    <string name="suz_HolyIntConv_des">It\'s a classic Suzdal picture: the whitewashed beauty of monastic walls surrounded by green meadows on the banks of the lazily meandering river.
        Inside are beds of brightly coloured flowers tended by the nuns, who live in wooden cottages left over from a rustic hotel built here when the convent was closed after the revolution
        (it was revived in 1992). Founded in 1364, this convent was originally a place of exile for the unwanted wives of tsars.</string>
    <string name="suz_ChurchAssump_des">This small red church up the street from the kremlin features a beautiful icon of the Virgin Mary created by 16th-century artist Fyodor Zubov,
        as well as a large gold-and-glass coffin containing the relics of St Arseny (1550–1625), the Archbishop of Suzdal.</string>


    <!-- Kostroma item name -->

    <string name="kos_MonIpaty_name">Monastery of St Ipaty</string>
    <string name="kos_MuseumWood_name">Museum of Wooden Architecture</string>
    <string name="kos_SusanPl_name">Susaninskaya Ploshchad</string>
    <string name="kos_Guardhouse_name">Guardhouse</string>
    <string name="kos_MonEpiphany_name">Monastery of the Epiphany</string>

    <!-- Kostroma item address -->

    <string name="kos_MonIpaty_adr">Kostroma, Prosveshheniya ul, 1,</string>
    <string name="kos_MuseumWood_adr">Kostroma, ul Prosveshcheniya 1b</string>
    <string name="kos_SusanPl_adr">Kostroma, Susaninskaya Ploshchad</string>
    <string name="kos_Guardhouse_adr">Kostroma, ul Lenina 1/2</string>
    <string name="kos_MonEpiphany_adr">Kostroma, ul Simanovskogo 26</string>

    <!-- Kostroma item descriptiom -->

    <string name="kos_MonIpaty_des">Named after St Ipaty (Hypatios) of Gangara, this monastery at the confluence of the Volga and Kostroma Rivers was founded in the 1330s by Chet,
        a Tatar prince who converted to Christianity. In 1590 his descendant, Tsar Boris Godunov, built its Trinity Cathedral (Троицкий собор),
        which contains more than 80 old frescoes by a school of 17th-century Kostroma painters, as well as some 20th-century additions.
        (The fresco in the southern part of the sanctuary depicts Chet’s baptism by St Ipaty.)</string>
    <string name="kos_MuseumWood_des">Essentially a large riverside park, this open-air museum comprises a large collection of old, rural wooden buildings moved here for preservation,
        including peasant families\' houses, cleverly engineered windmills and churches – many built without nails. Some buildings display various artefacts of rural life,
        and the grounds (which are open an hour later than the exhibits) are pleasant for strolling, listening to the chirping of resident frogs and admiring the handiwork of the artists.</string>
    <string name="kos_SusanPl_des">Picturesque Susaninskaya pl was built under Catherine the Great’s patronage after a fire in 1773 (based on, as legend says, the shape of her fan)
        and nicely revamped for the Romanov dynasty\'s 400-year anniversary in 2013. Its immense Italianate Trading Arcades used to house hundreds of shops selling goods shipped along the Volga in its heyday,
        some of which are still represented in its street names (flour, tobacco, fish, spices and milk). Today it houses Kostroma\'s central market.</string>
    <string name="kos_Guardhouse_des">Constructed in 1826, this small guardhouse was originally a brig to hold arrested soldiers until trial.
        During the Soviet era it was used as offices for various institutions, including a library and a registry office.
        Today it belongs to the Kostroma Museum Reserve and houses three separate exhibits on military history, with displays of weapons and uniforms (from both Russia and other countries)
        from the medieval era to modern times.</string>
    <string name="kos_MonEpiphany_des">The Monastery of the Epiphany is now the Archbishop of Kostroma\’s residence. The large cathedral in this 14th- to 19th-century complex is the city\’s main working church.
        The 13th-century icon of Our Lady of St Theodore, on the right-hand side of the iconostasis, is supposedly the source of many miracles.</string>

    <!-- Vladimir item name -->

    <string name="vla_AssumpCath_name">Assumption Cathedral</string>
    <string name="vla_OldVladMus_name">Old Vladimir Museum</string>
    <string name="vla_CathStDmitry_name">Cathedral of St Dmitry</string>
    <string name="vla_GeorgUl_name">Georgievskaya Ulitsa</string>
    <string name="vla_HisMus_name">History Museum</string>
    <string name="vla_GoldGate_name">Golden Gate</string>
    <string name="vla_CrysLacEm_name">Crystal, Lacquer Miniatures and Embroidery Museum</string>
    <string name="vla_SobPl_name">Sobornaya Ploschad</string>


    <!-- Vladimir item address -->

    <string name="vla_AssumpCath_adr">Vladimir, Bloshaya Moskovskaya ul 56</string>
    <string name="vla_OldVladMus_adr">Vladimir, ul Kozlov tup</string>
    <string name="vla_CathStDmitry_adr">Vladimir, Bolshaya Moskovskaya ul 60</string>
    <string name="vla_GeorgUl_adr">Vladimir, Georgievskaya ul</string>
    <string name="vla_HisMus_adr">Vladimir, Bolshaya Moskovskaya ul 64</string>
    <string name="vla_GoldGate_adr">Vladimir, Bolshaya Moskovskaya ul 1</string>
    <string name="vla_CrysLacEm_adr">Vladimir, Dvoryanskaya ul 2</string>
    <string name="vla_SobPl_adr">Vladimir, Sobornaya pl</string>

    <!-- Vladimir item description -->

    <string name="vla_AssumpCath_des">Set dramatically high above the Klyazma River, this simple but majestic piece of pre-Mongol architecture is the legacy of Prince Andrei Bogolyubsky,
        the man who began shifting power from Kyiv to northeastern Rus (which eventually evolved into Muscovy). A white-stone version of Kyiv’s brick Byzantine churches,
        the cathedral was constructed from 1158 to 1160, though it was rebuilt and expanded after a fire in 1185. It was added to Unesco's World Heritage List in 1992.</string>
    <string name="vla_OldVladMus_des">This red-brick former water tower contains a multistorey exhibit of everyday objects from Vladimir\'s history (no English signage);
        the display of old clocks and stopwatches is among the most interesting. But follow the curving staircase all the way up to find the real draw here:
        the observation deck, which offers magnificent 360-degree views of Vladimir, with the Klyazma River curling lazily off into the distance and gold church domes set against the surrounding blue sky and green fields.</string>
    <string name="vla_CathStDmitry_des">Built between 1193 and 1197, this exquisite, Unesco-listed white-stone cathedral represents the epitome of Russian stone carving.
        The attraction here is the cathedral’s exterior walls, which are covered in an amazing profusion of images.
        At their top centre, the north, south and west walls all show King David bewitching the birds and beasts with music.</string>
    <string name="vla_GeorgUl_des">This pedestrian-only street curving southwest from the main strip was lovingly recreated in 2015 as a brick-paved thoroughfare from the old days,
        dotted with souvenir stores, whimsical bronze statues of 19th-century locals and working water pumps; at its far end is the former water tower.
        It\'s a lovely place for a stroll – don't miss the broad viewing terraces at the eastern end, which offer stunning views of Assumption Cathedral (especially gorgeous floodlit at night).</string>
    <string name="vla_HisMus_des">This museum displays many remains and reproductions of the ornamentation from Vladimir\’s two cathedrals as part of an extensive exhibition covering
        the history of the town from Kyivan princes to the 1917 revolution. Particularly interesting are the artefacts upstairs, including a remarkable keyboardless typewriter from 1905.
        The red-brick edifice was purpose-built in 1902.</string>
    <string name="vla_GoldGate_des">In the 1160s Andrei Bogolyubsky built five defensive gates to guard his city; only this former western entrance survives.
        It was later restored and expanded under Catherine the Great. Up the narrow stone staircase, a military museum displays weapons and armour from the 1200s through WWII
        (plus a 1970s cosmonaut suit); the centrepiece is a slightly fusty diorama of Vladimir being ravaged by Mongols in 1238, set to flashing lights and dramatic narration
        (English version available upon request).</string>
    <string name="vla_CrysLacEm_des">Housed in the former Old Believers\' Trinity Church (1916), this museum features the crafts of Gus-Khrustalny and other nearby towns.
        The 1st floor displays a huge variety of crystal pieces (old and new), while upstairs is a collection of embroidered cloth and 19th-century lacquer boxes painted
        with scenes from Russian history. Keep an eye out for the particularly detailed 10-piece matryoshka (nesting doll) that\'s over a century old.
        A basement shop has a decent selection of crystal for sale.</string>
    <string name="vla_SobPl_des">The expanse of \'Cathedral Sq\' is at the heart of downtown Vladimir.
        Its 22m-tall monument was built for the 850th anniversary of the town\'s founding.
        Three bronze statues at each side of the obelisk represent past and present: a warrior of Rus looks west to the Golden Gate; an architect gazes southward at the Assumption Cathedral;
        and a modern-day worker looks east towards the town\'s industrial area.</string>



</resources>
